▍2026 美网 男单1/4决赛
兹维列夫 6-2 7-5 6-1 范德赞德舒尔普 · 赛后场上采访
Sasha, well done tonight.
萨沙 今晚打得漂亮
You're the only guy this year to make
你是今年唯一一个
the semifinals or better in all four majors,
四大满贯全都打进四强以上
including the win in Roland Garros
包括法网夺冠
and the finals in Wimbledon.
以及温网决赛
Is your mentality going
打大满贯的心态
into a major different than it is going
和打别的赛事
to any other event?
有什么不一样吗？
Yes and no.
是也不是
I think, you know,
我想
you saw that in the first two rounds
前两轮你们都看到了
when I really didn't play well.
我打得真的不好
I can rely
在大满贯我可以
on my physicality a bit more in majors
更多地依靠身体
than I can other tournaments, you know,
比在别的赛事更能靠它
and in other tournaments I would
换成别的赛事
have been out at the first round,
我首轮就出局了
but here I can fight back and play best
但在这里我能打满五盘
of five, play for four and a half hours
打四个半小时再反打回来
and somehow win the match
然后想办法赢下这场球
and somehow get into the tournament
想办法把自己带进状态
and then, you know,
接着
I start playing better throughout
我会在整个赛事里
the tournament and yeah,
越打越好
definitely happy to be in a semi-finals here.
能打进四强我当然很高兴
But of course, I want to I want to go further.
但我当然还想走得更远
A
那么
a big talking point this year
今年一个热门话题
has been these late night finishes.
就是这些深夜才结束的比赛
You've had a couple.
你就碰上过几场
You had one that finished at 2:15 a.m.
有一场打到凌晨两点十五
Can you take us through the routine
能讲讲那之后
after that?
你的流程吗？
When you're done at 2:15,
两点十五打完
do you have a full meal?
你会正经吃一顿吗？
What time do you actually get to bed?
实际几点才睡下？
Yeah.
是这样
I mean, you go to the ice bath,
你要去泡冰浴
you have a meal, you talk to the press,
吃饭 然后跟媒体聊
which you're part
你们也是其中
of, and unfortunately I hate doing,
一员 而我很不喜欢这件事
so, but that's that's okay.
不过那也没什么
And then afterwards, yeah,
再之后
you you get some treatment done
做一些治疗
and you go to bed.
然后去睡觉
I mean, I went to bed as late as 6:45 a.m.
最晚一次早上六点四十五才睡
in the last in the last week.
就在上个星期
So, I'm kind of a bit jetlagged.
所以我有点像在倒时差
I feel like I'm playing the Australian Open
感觉自己是在纽约
in New York right now.
打澳网
But, as long as I'm still here,
但只要我还留在这里
as long as I'm in the semi-finals,
只要我还在半决赛里
that's that's all that matters.
那就是最重要的
You're going
今晚你终于
to get a proper bedtime tonight.
能好好睡一觉了
Finally, you're in one of the best cities
你正待在世界上
in the world.
最好的城市之一
You're here every other night,
你隔一晚就来这儿
but the other nights,
那另外那些晚上呢
are you one to go out to dinners in the city
你会出去在城里吃个饭
and check out all the things
逛逛纽约
that New York has to offer?
有意思的地方吗？
I watched I watched Shelton Alcaraz until
我看谢尔顿打阿尔卡拉斯
3:30 a.m.
看到凌晨三点半
last night.
就在昨天晚上
I did not go to bed.
我根本没睡
I was up late.
我一直熬着
I was watching TV cuz I was sleeping
我在看电视 因为反正
in until 1:00 p.m.
我要睡到下午一点
Anyway, so credit to Ben.
总之要给本点个赞
He played an unbelievable match.
他那场球打得难以置信
And tomorrow after tomorrow,
还有后天
it's going to be, I think,
我想那会是
a fun semi-final between two Americans.
两个美国人之间的精彩半决赛
Yeah, we're excited for both.
我们对两边都很期待
Congratulations tonight
恭喜你今晚
into the semi-finals.
挺进半决赛
Sasha Zverev.
萨沙 兹维列夫